Now that I see that you're
up ahead, waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things!
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see what sort of
form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're bleeding!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you
as you finish what you've begun!
Let's do that wind to dry all the tears as
you're blaming the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure,
found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
I call this my chop-chop emergency escape!
Unwrapped like that should
break your skull just fine!
And this one here is my
aerial tailspin, Dadan!
You picked the wrong clown
to mess with, monkey!
No, don't get up!
Hey, hey, no clutching!
Damn, you got a lot stronger,
didn't you, kid? I don't know.
These guys are pretty tough.
What are they?
Sea monkeys.
Blue Gorillas, they're called.
Or Blue Carrot for short.
But stay shot.
Should be four more of them
left to take the place.
Well, never mind.
I guess you got them already.
Either way, I hope
that's the last of them.
I don't have time to
mess around right now.
That guy's a monster.
How did he do that?
You came here to let us out, didn't you?
We'll be your best friend, pal.
I promise.
Something wrong you bet
there is i thought you
said only one prisoner
escaped yeah it was just
the clown guy pretty
sure i saw two guys but
maybe i'm crazy and speaking
of crazy five blue got
taken down in front of
community cell number 10
on level one there's no
way the prisoners down
there aren't strong
enough to take on even one
blue goldie you're broken
here to rescue me yep
we gotta stay quiet i'm
not really following
your own advice there we
could well use the keys
to our cell if you're
not too busy shut the
hell up nobody gives a
damn wait do you know ace
yeah and though i can see the resemblance
he made a better impression than you did?
He's sleeping!
After he woke up, we had a few drinks,
chatted it up, and became pretty good pals.
So yeah, I think it sucks your
brother got thrown in here too.
Kind of stupid of the Navy to do that.
I'm sure Whitebeard will give him hell.
I heard they're keeping Ace on level 5.
Could you show me the way to get there?
Not a chance in hell!
Go by yourself!
What, do you think I'm your friend now?
In fact, you can die
down here for all I care.
So long.
If you don't want to break out of
here, I'll just do it on my own.
Okay, but there's ten
battleships out there.
I hope you've got a good plan.
That's not good.
All right, I get it.
They must be expecting an
attack from Whitebeard.
Guess I picked a bad time.
Maybe I could just lay low.
I'll find someone else then.
So are we getting the key or not?
No, no, I must be imagining things.
What would he be doing
with something like that?
Then again.
Well, good luck with your escape.
I gotta get moving.
No, that's gotta be it.
Quite strong!
What's your problem?
Up there!
No kidding, because you
won't stop yelling so much!
By the way, that's a lovely armlet
you've got there, Straw Hat.
Do you think you can give
it to me, pretty please?
No, it was a gift from Nami.
What do you want with it?
If you let me have the armlet,
I'll tell you how to get to this.
That a promise? Sure.
Just fork it over, kiddo.
Okay, you got a deal.
All right!
First off, let's shake those guards.
Grab onto my feet, okay?
Your feet.
Good, now start running!
Be careful with those!
Can't have you chop them!
Let's review how Buggy's
chop-chop power works, shall we?
When he chop-chops his body to pieces,
he can control each part however he
likes, but only within a limited area.
And if his feet aren't
close to the ground,
he becomes unable to levitate
the rest of his body.
I am one lucky clown!
Captain Captain
What?
I'm just starting to have second
thoughts about this place.
That's all.
You sure this is the cave where
Captain John kept his hidden treasure?
And the crew he left behind
never found it this whole time?
It seems a bit too easy.
Just hold the lantern and
keep walking. Yes, sir.
Now look alive, boys!
The treasure is near, but
so is unspeakable danger!
If you let your guard down, even for a
second, then death will creep up on you.
There's no telling what
kind of monsters will appear
or what vicious booby
traps await to kill us all.
Come on, men!
Another fine day!
Carving out tunnels awaits us.
Right?
Oh, boss.
Oh, you three must be the new guys.
Nothing like working up
a sweat, right, boss?
All a man really needs is a pickaxe
in his hand and a tunnel to dig.
That's right.
And because of our good
old-fashioned elbow grease,
everyone who comes to
this tunnel will smile.
It's liberating.
You know, after all this, hardly.
But we ought to hit it with
the old bilge barge for a...
How dare you make me work
like one of your lackeys!
Unfortunately, that wasn't the first dead
end we hit, and it wouldn't be the last.
We ran all over the Grand Line
looking for that treasure.
As if that wasn't crappy enough,
my ill-fated treasure hunts brought
me straight to a navy post one day,
and the bastards threw me in
this dump when they captured me.
But maybe it was destiny all along,
guiding me to Captain John's treasure.
Step on it, stride.
Hard times are wasted.
Follow me and we'll be
at level two in no time.
Level two?
Were you listening to me?
I said I wanted to go to level five.
Don't you know how numbers work?
You gotta go through two to
get to five. Let me explain.
Think of this as an upside-down tower.
The place we're in right now is called level
one, which is the first basement floor.
After that, you go to level
two and level three and so on.
The deeper you get, the more
infamous the criminals are.
They tortured me in the fires
of level four a few times,
but that's as far as I've gone myself.
Everything else is just things
I've heard from other people.
Level five is where they take
all the big shots, though.
So in a bounty as high as your
brother's, he's gotta be there.
As for what's below level 5,
well, I've heard some rumors,
but the details are scarce.
The theory is the criminals
they send down there are so
dangerous that they've been
completely wiped from history.
Now that I think about it,
there's a good chance that's
where they took your brother.
But the furthest I can take you is level
4, so you're on your own after that.
Thanks, Buggy.
I thought you were a real
jerk, but I guess I was wrong.
A deal's a deal.
And if that armor leads me
to Captain John's treasure,
I'm getting a real bargain, kid.
I shouldn't have opened my big mouth.
If you got caught, you're
a pretty crappy pirate.
What the hell, man?
Give me a break.
The idiot didn't even hear me.
I'm lucky he's so stupid. That's awesome.
This is a treasure map?
I didn't have a clue.
Bet that'll be really fun. Huh.
Sorry, kid, but if you know the
truth, I'll have to kill you.
You better take this now
in case I forget later!
You know that's a treasure map, and
you're still gonna give it to me?
Yeah, of course,
treasure's cool and all, but Ace is more
important But if you give it to me now,
what's to stop me from running off with
it and leaving you down here to die?
Nothing, I guess, but you
gave your word you'd help out,
and that's good enough for me
Ha ha!
Those drastic eyes pouring into my soul!
Hermit Skelgril's straw
hat, can't you see?
Don't do it!
You deserve better than this!
I'm no good for you!
After all this time,
I finally have the key to Captain
John's secret, and I own all to you!
Thanks, buddy.
You're a real champ!
Now how do I ditch you and
get the hell out of here?
Oh, if we break through the walls
here, is it like a shortcut?
I can do that!
What's wrong with you?
What the hell is going on in here?
That clown is bugging
the escaped prisoner.
But who is that other guy?
Oh, no, this is the guard room.
If we keep going this way, I'm in trouble.
For crap's sake, please stop!
This place is crazy.
I mean, there's a forest in the prison?
And why is everything all red?
Who are those guys down there?
They're prisoners, stupid.
This so-called forest
is a torture chamber.
Every leaf is as sharp as a razor.
That's why they call them blade trees.
And the grass is made of spikes
that creak you like needles.
It's called spike needle grass.
Original, I know.
The jailers release
venomous spiders and chase
the prisoners up and down
the forest all day long.
Deadly pitchforks behind them,
piercing needles beneath them?
and cutting razors everywhere else.
They run until they're
drenched in their own blood,
suffering agonies they
never thought possible.
This is level one, otherwise known as the
Crimson Hell, the true face of Impel Down.
Haven't I suffered enough?
You're gonna kill me.
Wow, this place really is like hell.
Are they doing this kind
of stuff to Ace, too?
Don't think about it.
Just keep falling. That's dumb.
I'm gonna get cut.
Oh, yeah.
Watch this!
Listen up, kid.
Now take my feet and throw them
down on the ground right below us.
Are you sure?
Okay.
Holy crap, you don't see that every day.
Whoa, careful!
Are you kidding me?
This is a cinch.
And the good news is, we don't need to go
down any stairs to get to the next level.
No stairs, no gate, no
key, just free-falling.
The normal prisoners
wouldn't want to take it,
but there is one way to
get out of the Crimson
Hill that'll be perfect
for our little plot.
Okay, take your word for it.
See, we're already here.
Whoa?
Whoa, I can't see a thing!
Like I said, there's a way out.
but nobody wants to take it.
Can you guess why?
It's not because it's dark and scary.
It's because this hole is a
one-way trip down to level two.
And if you think things are bad here,
well, you ain't seen nothing yet, kiddo.
When people get sent to hell, you better
believe they'll try to claw their way out.
But no one in their right mind would ever
dream of diving further into the abyss.
Yeah, I get it.
And it's a good thing we're crazy.
So just jump down, huh?
Yeah, but be careful, there's a...
Are you kidding me?
Whoa, it's deep!
What do you think's down there?
Geez, would you give it a minute, kid?
You got huge balls or just a tiny brain?
Well, this works out for me.
Now I can blow this joint and
he can't say a damn thing.
I got the key to the treasure.
I got that chump off my
back and soon I'll be free.
I'd say see you in hell, buddy!
But I've been there and done that.
I robbed you, got my revenge,
and you thanks me for it?
Stupid you can't chop me.
What do you think the
chop-chop fruit is for?
Crap!
Those are my feet!
No! No!
Please, you feet!
Not that!
Surveillance troop, come in!
We sighted another escapee.
He and Buggy both fell to level two.
Can you find him?
I'm on it.
Hey, is it just me?
The beasts seem kind of restless today.
As long as they're not
hungry, anything but that.
I'm too tired to be afraid
anymore, I don't even care.
I'm going to be there at
dinner sooner or later,
it might as well be today, I suppose.
Holy crap!
Now that's a wild beast of hell!
Wait, I know that face.
Dammit, the rumors are true.
This thing's gonna eat us whole.
Why am I even here?
I didn't want to go to level
two in the first place.
I was trying to escape
and leave you behind.
You're bad luck.
Everything that sucks in
my life is all your fault.
What?
Did you say something?
And what is this thing chasing us?
From the looks of it, I'd say it's the
rarest kind of monster in existence.
A snake born from a chicken egg.
A basilisk.
That thing came out of a chicken.
I said it was a monster, didn't I?
These things shouldn't be allowed
to live, let alone run free.
They eat people like snacks,
so they lock them up here where
they can only eat criminals.
What are you doing?
I don't have time for this, Snakebird.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
It's getting hot. Well,
as the Vice Warden told you before,
the Warden's office is located on Level 4,
which is known as the Burning Heat Floor.
Aside from his office, the
whole floor is an inferno.
There, we finally arrived.
Well, where is he?
Where is this Warden?
Warden Magellan suffers from
terrible digestive problems,
so he stays in the bathroom
an average of ten hours a day,
seven days a week.
Of course, he sleeps about
eight hours each night.
So once you factor in mealtimes and breaks,
he only works about four hours a day.
Is that really enough time to do his job?
When the need arises, he's the right man.
Oh, we're in luck, sounds
like he's coming out.
And I forgot to mention it before,
but the warden ate the venom
venom fruit, so he's a poison man.
Poison man?
Yes, please be careful.
Excellent work in there, warden.
You showed those bowels.
Who's boss, sir?
Oh!
As always, it was a rough battle in there.
You must be our guests.
I'm Magellan, the warden here.
Oh, this room is too bright.
For the record, I much prefer places
that are dark, cold, and closed off.
Just like my heart.
Stop being ridiculous. Now listen.
Vice Admiral Momonga and the warlord Boa
Hancock are here on important business.
And our time is short, Warden Magellan.
Ah, my apologies.
I have a bad case of the runs, I'm afraid.
The poison soup I had for breakfast this
morning isn't quite agreeing with me.
Well, what do you expect?
It's poison.
Oh, come on.
I'm a poison man.
I love poison.
It's just like the old saying goes.
Poison kills poison, I believe.
Well, that's why you
have venomous diarrhea.
Yes, and I'm afraid that you
have a venomous tongue, Hannibal.
Hurry up and retire so
I can become Warden.
Pass, I mean, uh, please hurry
and show our guest a fire fist.
Yeah, right, like that
was a slip of the tongue.
It saddens my heart to know that
my calling thinks so little of me.
Put these on.
Warden, please be careful when you exhale.
Your breath is poisonous gas.
Are you trying to kill everyone?
Hey, what the hell is so funny?
Sir, you're right.
Stupid Vice Warden.
And I have the venomous tongue?
Fool!
You dare breathe your disgusting
poison in the face of an empress?
How rude!
She's stepping on me,
and I think I like it.
Lucky punk.
Vice Warden, you realize that's
the warden's seat you're in.
It'll be mine soon enough.
We don't have time for this.
Yes, this is the warden's office.
Hey, don't answer my phone.
Oh no i'm dying damn it i
just wanted to be warden
retrieve an antidote for
the vice warden right
What's that you say someone
broke into the prison absurd
this is impelled down no
one has ever Infiltrated its
walls our defenses are
flawless how could we possibly
allow this it is indeed A
travesty and it was on your watch
warden have they found
us out transfer the video
footage To my chambers warden
i was wondering would it be
possible to see the prisoner
now sure let's go Like right
now warden wake up we kind
of need you to deal with this
Now that's odd it appears that
we've lost contact with warden
magellan i want to report on
every Level of this place sent
to the jailer's room and navy
headquarters now i don't know
why he's here And i have no
clue what he might be up to but
that guy who's wreaking so
much havoc with buggy the Clown
on level two is definitely straw
hat luffy something's up we
lost contact with the jailer's
Room on level two what jailer's
room on level two what's going
on down there what's wrong
His fist!
It was huge!
Why in the hell are you so small?
Because I used their gear.
Takes care of him.
There we go! I'm back!
Okie Dock, let's get moving!
The god of salvation
has descended into hell!
He beat the basilisk!
I saw it myself!
Yes!
The monster is down!
He got him!
You did it!
You guys are amazing!
They destroyed the jailers' room, too!
It's a miracle!
There must be angels sent from heaven!
I don't know who you
two are, but thank you!
Hey, guys, could you
hand us those keys, too?
They're for these cuffs in the doors!
They're right there!
See them?
Over there on the ground!
What's he doing?
Come on!
We gotta get going!
Don't be in such a rush!
You're supposed to be saving my brother!
That Straw Hat Luffy!
What is he doing down here?
He's not in a cell nor
in a prison uniform,
and it looks like he's on his
way out of here! All right,
an opportunity like this one simply
won't happen again, it's now or never!
As much as I thought otherwise, it seems
heaven hasn't forsaken me just yet!
Hey, boys!
Is this what you're looking for?
Yeah!
Give it to me!
Let us out of here! Hmm?
Now is that any way to
ask someone for a favor?
We're sorry!
We're begging you!
All right, you got it!
One set of keys coming right up!
Compliments of Captain Buggy!
Accept it with gratitude!
You're free! You're free!
That's right!
Now I ask you,
what's the glorious name of the man
who has given you your sweet freedom?
It's Captain Buggy and
we're in your debt forever
anybody talking bad about
Buggy's gonna answer
to us that's me and don't
you scum ever forget
it now unlock the other
cells set everyone free
once these morons start
making havoc on this place
I'll finally have a chance
to sneak out on my own
hey what the hell are you doing
those guys are my turn put me down
stupid leave me down to the next
level last time or something how
should I know this place is like
a maze you expect me to remember
the details of every floor
five-year-old damn way to level three
Thanks for everything, Captain Buggy!
I can smell freedom already!
Stop it, sir!
Put me down! Shut up!
You said you'd leave me all the way down
to level four, and now you're gonna do it!
I lied, okay?
I just wanted the treasure,
so I lied to get it!
With all those prisoners free,
the chaos will be immeasurable
And when that happens, I'll...
Wait, what was that? You lied? Yeah!
What are you idiots doing?
You're free!
This is your chance to race
hell and get out of here!
We, uh, we just remembered
why we never tried to do that.
Escape is impossible, especially with
those wild beasts running around!
Yeah, dying is for the birds.
We're way better off in this set.
Okay, I've changed my mind, Straw Hat.
I'll show you the way to level three here.
Let's go. What?
But you just said you didn't
know the way, Big Nose.
My nose is perfect. How rude.
I couldn't help but overhear you.
If you're having trouble
on this floor, I can help.
Is that so? Who are you?
Long time no see, Straw Hat Luffy.
You helped me out without
noticing. How fortunate.
I am a man who always pays back his debts.
Do I know you?
Wait, it's the three hair.
Oh, I'm just a little
game of hide and see.
Oh, yeah.
You were on the island
with the giants, right?
Three. Mr.
Three, you fool.
Strike me!
I've no regrets!
That violent oaf!
Yeah, Captain. I'm sorry.
That's the brakes.
My body is fine.
My heart, however, craves justice.
My heart wants war!
Jinbei, I can't die.
Not here and not like this.
To hell with my title as a warlord.
I don't even want it anymore.
If it means that I could stop this fight,
I would happily lay down my own life.